

+61 434 727 121





olivia.kotova@hotmail.com

Australian citizen

Education

Diploma in Website Development (TAFE South Bank, QLD) — Jun 2021-Jul 2022

Summary

Being full of energy I'm looking for employment in IT industry. Having genuine interest in IT, began exploring deeply that area couple years ago to make a career change. Aiming to achieve sufficient foundation to become a professional I graduated at TAFE South Bank with Diploma in Web Development where I gained hands-on experience with JavaScript, ReactJS, NodeJS, Data Structures, APIs, SQL and non SQL (MongoDB) database, Bootstrap and tech principles and culture via both team/individual projects, code reviews and presentations. I believe my passion in solving complex tasks by applying modern IT solutions will be an asset to your company.

Proficiency

- WordPress (1.5 year of professional use)
- JavaScript (1 year during studying Diploma Web Dev)
- Adobe Suite (7 years of professional use)
- · Familiarity with cloud computing concepts

Soft Skills

- Highly developed organisational and time management skills
- Troubleshooting
- Have an eye for detail
- Industrious
- Punctual and reliable
- Self-motivated

Experience:

Graphic Designer and Photo Retoucher at Koshka Media Pty Ltd (Sydney, Australia) — Sep 2019 - Present time (casual)

koshkamedia.com is one of the greatest company to provide high quality services for wedding and family photos and films in Sydney. I'm honoured to help remotely at the Prema Photo & Video and give a hand when necessary by utilising my expertise and knowledge in:

- Retouching photos
- Image composition
- Builded the website koshkamedia.com

Graphic Designer at Africa Studio (Mykolayiv, Ukraine) - Dec 2014 - Aug 2017

Africa Studio is one of the leading companies producing and selling tens of thousands professional stock photos and designs within impressive variety of topics at platforms such as Shutterstock (https://stock.adobe.com/contributor/293313/ africa-studio and others as well.

- Prepared various artwork for digital development and commercial use
- Creating designs by mixing different photos for specified topics and making them seamless and immaculate
- Colour matching and creating banners for advertising
- Was mentoring new employees when required

✓ Achievements:

- My final designed work were the highest selling items
- Increased company's standards of quality
- Reduced the cost of design due to fast work